Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.
Magical Girl
This is the story of a young girl
who was obsessed with an anime...
Sara-sara-saate!!
Sarasarasate: spell name
For love and justice!
Manami-chan!
Hey, don't go ahead by yourself.
Oh, Yoko-san!
Ah, it's been a while.
Hello auntie!
Manami-chan,
what cute clothes you're wearing.
Mommy just bought them for me!
I see!
You seem to be doing much better.
Ah, yes. It's already been two months, after all...
Well,
if you ever need anything...
Alright.
Come on, Manami-chan, say goodbye too.
What's wrong?
Um, you see...
that man over there,
is possessed by a Hakketsuma.
Hakketsuma: Blood-Crazed Demon
Possessed by a what?
Look this.
Here.
Did it happen in the anime?
It's a bad guy from an anime
that controls humans and
makes them do terrible things!
Heh, is that so?
Yeah! If we don't beat him with magic,
something awful will happen!
Hmm...
But I have to go home and prepare dinner.
Let's defeat him another time, okay?
Ehhh...
We're having curry tonight,
and you love that—
Huh? He's gone?
He's always targeting Mommy...
Anyway, let's hurry home!
The Hakketsuma,
has dark darkness power!
Just hurry up.
Nothing can defeat him except for shiny light magic!
I get it already.
So we have to fight—
ENOUGH with the Hakketsuma stuff, Manami!
What do you mean, "fight"?
It's okay.
I'll protect you, Mommy!
Because I'm a Magical Girl!
N-No!
Reality isn't like anime!
This isn't pretend play like you used to do with Daddy!
Mommy, behind you!
AH!
AHHHHHHH!
Stay away!
M-My body is moving on its own...!
I'll protect Mommy!
Manami!
Sara-sara-saate!
For love and justice!
(The monster/entity gets exorcised/defeated by the magical chant)
Why...?
AAAAAHHHHH!
Just now...
Yoko-san!
Mother!
what a terrible thing to go through!
Daddy...
let's play again sometime!
Even at a time like this, she's still dreaming...
No... it wasn't a dream.
Huh?
The Hakketsuma was that person...
And surely, from heaven, to make Manami happy...
Yoko-san...
Key Scene Note: In this episode, the line between child play and supernatural reality blurs. Manami's father passed away two months prior. While her mother thinks Manami is merely immersing herself in anime pretend-play to cope with grief, a real malignant entity ("Hakketsuma") was actually targeting the mother. In the end, it is implied that the deceased father's spirit temporarily took over/assisted in order to protect them, using the "magical girl" power play to save his family from heaven.
THE END
Key scene note: In this episode, the line between child play and supernatural reality blurs. Manami's father passed away two months prior.
While her mother thinks Manami is merely immersing herself in anime pretend-play to cope with grief, a real malignant entity ("Hakketsuma") was actually targeting the mother.
In the end, it is implied that the deceased father's spirit temporarily took over/assisted in order to protect them, using the "magical girl" power play to save his family from heaven.
However, the monstrous roar at the very end implies that the exorcism was only temporary. The dark entity remains, leaving the family in lingering danger without their protector.
Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.